<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="iop" >
        Iops are courageous knights who
        let their weapons do the talking.
        If they knew what proverbs were,
        their favorite would definitely be
        "Act before you think." Unfortunately,
        the size of their brains is inversely
        proportional to the size of their swords...
        Still, Iops are great protectors who are always appreciated
        in groups. Plus, they have such beautiful hair!\n
    </string>
    <string name="cra" >
    If the Cras had a motto, it would probably be
        "Pride and precision." Specializing in long-distance combat,
        these skilled archers are precious allies who have more than
        one string to their bow when it comes to keeping enemies back.
        Their greatest pleasure is firing feathered arrows into hastily
        retreating buttocks...\n
    </string>
    <string name="ecaflip" >
        Ecaflips are compulsive gamblers
        who jump headlong into risky situations
        just for the thrill of it! Oh, and contrary to
        what you might have heard, they dont
        always land on their feet... Not that they care,
        as long as the adrenaline keeps pumping!
        So, ready to up the ante?\n
    </string>
    <string name="feca" >
     Fecas are born protectors.
        When a friend has entrusted them with something,
        you will never get it off them - not even over
        their dead body! They fight tirelessly to keep their
        allies safe. Oh, and you should think twice before picking
        off any stray Gobballs: Fecas may not be shepherds any more,
        but its still in their nature to stand guard over any vulnerable
        creature targeted by a vicious attacker...\n
    </string>
    <string name="pandawa" >
        Always willing to lend a hand and put
    n a little elbow grease, Pandawas are strong
    and nimble carriers... whether its to bring over
        a fresh tray of drinks or to lift up an enemy
        andsend them flying! One thingsfor sure -
        spend some time with a Pandawa,and you will soon be seeing stars...\n
    </string>
    <string name="steam" >
      Patient and prudent, a good Foggernaut
        will wait for just the right moment to strike...
        Over the centuries, they have come on in leaps
        and bounds, both intellectually and physically.
        Born of a clan of warlike atheists, they have
        evolved to become the ambassadors of a peace-loving people.
        Their mission is to track down Stasili mines in order to
        prepare for the grand return of their kin...\n
    </string>
    <string name="sram" >
        A good mask is a must-have for all
        sneaky behavior - and nobody knows
        that better than the Srams! They can whip a
        loaded money-pouch out of an adventurer
        pocket in a flash and run rings around
        enemies that step on their toes. In short,
        when the Srams come out to play, its probably
        better to stay at home...\n
    </string>
    <string name="enutrof" >
       	That healthy golden glow,that warm,
        balmy scent, those perfect curves...
        No Enutrof can resist a shiny new kama!
        Gifted with an unfailing sense of greed,
        they will move earth and sky with their
        shovels when there is treasure at stake,
        which makes them great teammates...
        if you can look past their bad temper
        and shocking hygiene.\n
    </string>
</resources>